Clayton Hebenik

UI/UX Designer & Front-end Developer



+1.587.434.4847



www.claytonhebenik.com



clayton.hebenik@gmail.com

About

I'm a designer and front-end developer with a passion for crafting user-centered experiences that are memorable and exciting to use. I love tackling new challenges in digital production and outside work; especially in skateboarding and hiking.

Highlights:

- 5 years experience designing and coding web solutions
- Background in Web Design and Front-end Development
- Experienced collaborating in teams and working independently as a freelancer.

Skills + Knowledge



UI/UX Design

Interface Design Adobe Creative Suite Digital Prototyping Lo-Fi Prototypina User Experience **Usability Testing**



Front-end Dev

HTML5/CSS3 jQuery/JavaScript Bootstrap Wordpress Sitefinity



Collaboration

Presenting Ideation Agile/Scrum

Education



Masters of Digital Media (MDM)

Centre for Digital Media, Vancouver, BC

Master's degree in technical management and agile leadership. Jointly awarded by the University of British Columbia, Simon Fraser University, Emily Carr University of Art + Design and the British Columbia Institute of Technology.

2016 - Present



🗫 New Media, BFA

University of Lethbridge, Lethbridge, AB

Bachelors degree in digital media technologies and their creative application, including graphic design, web development, video production, and 3D modelling.

2007 - 2011

Professional Experience



Web Designer + Front-end Developer

Freelance

2016 - Present

Design and code web solutions to meet client needs. Effectively communicate designs, deliverables, and expectations.

thehardtimes.net | nomme.ca | urban-realty.ca



Web Designer + Front-end Developer

Anderweb, Calgary, AB

2011 - 2016

Collaborated with development team and stakeholders to design, code and launch client web solutions for local businesses, ecommerce, and database management.

MDM Project Experience



UX Designer

Client: Twist Performance + Wellness

May 2017 - Aug 2017

Mobile application allowing users to set and track

Design and test core interactions with rapid prototyping, competetive research, user research, usability testing.



UI/UX Designer

Project: Planet Creator Virtual Reality Game Client: Fire-Point Interactive

Jan 2017 – Apr 2017

Game for HTC Vive teaching children about the composition and formation of planets.

Designed and implemented UI elements. Collaborated with team on rapid prototyping and experience design. Communicated design with storyboards and documentation. Facilitated user tests to direct design decisions.